<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on WELCOME</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on WELCOME</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/hero_carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/hero_carousel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic</title>
      <link>/home/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/hero/</guid>
      <description>The highly flexible website framework for Hugo with an extensible plugin mechanism. Create a beautifully simple site in under 10 minutes 🚀 Latest release   Star</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Rui Hou is a professor at Institute of Information Engineering, CAS.  Interests  Computer Architecture Processor chip design Hardware Security Artificial Intelligence  About  Dr. Rui Hou’s major research interest includes CPU architecture and security, as well as data center server design. Before joined IIE, he was a processor of Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences. He published over 30 papers in international conferences and journals, and got more than 50 patents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/home/about-extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about-extra/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Rui Hou is a professor at Institute of Information Engineering, CAS. His major research interest includes CPU architecture and security, as well as data center server design. Before joined IIE, he was a processor of Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences. He published over 30 papers in international conferences and journals, and got more than 50 patents. Rui has also served more than ten times on conference organizing committees in international academia community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honors</title>
      <link>/home/honors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/honors/</guid>
      <description> National Science Foundation of China for Excellent Young Scholars, China, 2015 Journal of Parallel and Distributed Computing, Associate Editor HPCA 2019, TPC HPCA 2018, TPC PACT 2018, TPC ISPASS 2019 TPC Euro-par 2014, TPC Program Co-Chair, Computing Frontier 2015 Micro 2018, Publicity co-chair HPCA 2013, Web Chair PPoPP 2013, Local Chair Organizer, EDCS (Efficient Data Center System), 2012-2015, co-held with HPCA and ISCA Organizer, Built-in security workshop, co-held with CCS 2018 and HPCA 2019 Member of Computer Architecture，CCF Associate Editor, Journal of Parallel and Distributed Computing Web chair, HPCA 2011 Local Chair, PPoPP 2011  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/experience/</guid>
      <description> Professor  Institute of Information Engineering,CAS Leading the data center server and Artificial Intelligence workloads optimization team March 2017 - Present  Professor  Institute of Computing Technology,CAS Leading the team to design cost-effective data center server architecture March 2011 - March 2017  Staff Researcher  IBM China Research Center Participate in the development of big data and streaming system March 2007 - March 2011   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>