<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on WELCOME</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on WELCOME</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/hero_carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/hero_carousel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic</title>
      <link>/home/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/hero/</guid>
      <description>The highly flexible website framework for Hugo with an extensible plugin mechanism. Create a beautifully simple site in under 10 minutes 🚀 Latest release   Star</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>  Rui Hou is a professor at Institute of Information Engineering, CAS.  Interests  Computer Architecture Processor chip design Hardware Security Artificial Intelligence  Education  PhD Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences 2007 Master Harbin Institute of Technology 2003 Bachelor Harbin Institute of Technology 2001  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/home/about-extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about-extra/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Rui Hou is a professor at Institute of Information Engineering, CAS. His major research interest includes CPU architecture and security, as well as data center server design. Before joined IIE, he was a processor of Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences. He published over 30 papers in international conferences and journals, and got more than 50 patents. Rui has also served more than ten times on conference organizing committees in international academia community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honors</title>
      <link>/home/honors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/honors/</guid>
      <description> Organizer, EDCS (Efficient Data Center System), 2012-2015, co-held with HPCA and ISCA Associate Editor, Journal of Parallel and Distributed Computing Program Co-Chair, Computing Frontier 2015 PC Member, HPCA 2019, HPCA 2018, PACT 2018, ISPASS 2019, Euro-par 2014 Publicity chair, Micro 2018 Web chair, HPCA 2011 Local Chair, PPoPP 2011  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/experience/</guid>
      <description>Researcher Ph.D.supervisor  Institute of Information Engineering,CAS Leading for the Research Team of Processor Chip Security Architecture March 2017 - Present  Researcher Ph.D.supervisor  Institute of Computing Technology,CAS Director of CPU Laboratory, Advanced Computer System Research Center Developing Next Generation Data Center Server System and Core Chip National Natural Science Foundation, Academy of Sciences Strategic Pilot Project Huawei-Institute of Computing Strategic Cooperation March 2011 - March 2017  Vice President  Suzhou Zhongshenghongxin IT Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>